http://www.hmbreview.com/site/privacy.html

Submit a Legal Notice
Why does SEO matter to you?
Half Moon Bay, CA
(94019)
Today
Partly cloudy skies early will give way to cloudy skies late. Low 44F. Winds NW at 5 to 10 mph..
Tonight
Partly cloudy skies early will give way to cloudy skies late. Low 44F. Winds NW at 5 to 10 mph.
Coronavirus
HALF MOON BAY REVIEW PRIVACY POLICYThis policy explains how HALF MOON BAY REVIEW may collect, use and aggregate personal information about you on WWW.HMBREVIEW.COM. HALF MOON BAY REVIEW respects your personal privacy and is committed to protecting it. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact HALF MOON BAY REVIEW in one of the following ways:Mailing Address:HALF MOON BAY REVIEW | 714 Kelly Avenue Half Moon Bay, CA 94019 | P: 650-726-4424For each visitor to the WWW.HMBREVIEW.COMsite, HALF MOON BAY REVIEW's servers automatically collect information about which pages are visited and the IP address or domain name of visitors. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web Site. Your IP address is not linked to personally identifiable information but is used to gather broad demographic information. This information helps us tailor and improve your experience on the Web Site.INFORMATION WE COLLECTGeneral: Portions of HALF MOON BAY REVIEW require visitors to provide personally identifiable information that may include your name, age, address, e-mail address, credit-card number and facts about your consumer-buying habits. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.Surveys: We conduct periodic online surveys. For example, visitors to WWW.HMBREVIEW.COM may see a pop-up window asking them to voluntarily participate in a user survey.Web site usage:We automatically collect IP addresses and web site usage information from you when you visit our site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our web sites on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each web page, the length of their visits, their browser type and their operating systems.HOW WE USE INFORMATION THAT IS COLLECTEDHALF MOON BAY REVIEW may use information collected from visitors in the following ways:* To improve existing features or develop new features, products and services by analyzing how site features are being used.* To award prizes in contests or promotions. Participation in some contests or promotions may require visitors to agree to be contacted by HALF MOON BAY REVIEW.* To provide advertisers or other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. Personally identifiable information is kept private and not distributed to third parties.* To send e-mail notifications about new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you. These contacts are on an opt-in basis only, based on the preferences you have specified with HALF MOON BAY REVIEW.CHILDREN/DIRECT NOTICE TO PARENTSHALF MOON BAY REVIEW will not knowingly collect any personal information from individuals under 13 years of age without parental consent. Where appropriate, HALF MOON BAY REVIEW will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our site and/or will take reasonable steps to ensure parental consent to such submission.Parental consent will be required in the event HALF MOON BAY REVIEW provides a feature or event such as a contest or promotion that requires submission of information by children. Notice may be provided in a number of ways, including sending an e-mail message or notice by postal mail. At any time, you may write to us at publisher@coastsidenewsgroup.com to request a summary of any information we have retained as part of such activities or to ask that it be deleted.Parents should be aware that HALF MOON BAY REVIEW's Privacy Policy will govern our use of personal data, but that information which is voluntarily given by children (or others) in chat sessions, e-mail exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited mail. HALF MOON BAY REVIEW encourages all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal data while using the Internet.COOKIESHALF MOON BAY REVIEW may place a "cookie"; on the browser of your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common in the Internet industry, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features to their customers. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information, but may be used to tell when your computer has contacted the HALF MOON BAY REVIEW site. HALF MOON BAY REVIEW uses the information for editorial purposes and for other purposes such as delivery of features and advertisements, so that HALF MOON BAY REVIEW can customize delivery of information specific to your interests without compromising privacy. For example, cookies may be used to ensure that you will not see the same ads too often in a single session. We also may use cookies to save your passwords so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit portions of our site.REGISTRATIONHALF MOON BAY REVIEW requires voluntary registration. These forms require you to give us personally identifiable information, which may include contact information (like your name and e-mail address) and unique identifiers. If you so signify beforehand, we may use your contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. Unique identifiers are collected only for use as account numbers in our record system. We do not disclose any unique identifiers to any third parties.The information collected from these registration forms is used to improve existing features or develop new features, products and services by analyzing how site features are being used. Such information may be shared with third parties on an aggregate basis.DEMOGRAPHIC AND PROFILE DATAWe also may collect demographic and profile data from you as part of the registration process (i.e., your ZIP code, sex, income level, interest in certain topics). We may use this data to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content we think you might be interested in, displaying the content according to your preferences and informing you of upcoming events on our site. We also share certain demographic and profile data with advertisers and business partners on an aggregated basis.HALF MOON BAY REVIEW will disclose account information only in special cases, such as (i) to comply with valid legal requirements, such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (ii) when HALF MOON BAY REVIEW has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or harm to HALF MOON BAY REVIEW users or other persons or violating the Terms of Service of this site.LINKSThis site contains links to other sites. HALF MOON BAY REVIEW is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with HALF MOON BAY REVIEW (such as co-branded pages and "powered by" relationships) or the sites of HALF MOON BAY REVIEW advertisers that you go to by clicking on a banner ad on the WWW.HMBREVIEW.COMsite. HALF MOON BAY REVIEW does not disclose unique identifiers to those responsible for the linked sites. The linked sites, however, may collect personal information from you when you link to their site. This collecting of information is not subject to HALF MOON BAY REVIEW's control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policy of the sites you visit by linking from our Web Site.ADVERTISEMENTSWe display advertisements on our Web Site. These ads may contain cookies. We do not have access to this information, nor do we control its use. HALF MOON BAY REVIEW does not provide any personally identifiable data regarding users to our advertisers.Third-Party AdvertisersWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the Website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third-party ad servers’ and networks’ Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please follow the following links: http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/, or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.We may allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements, and we may use any of the Non-Personally Identifying Information we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser.SECURITYThis site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.EMAIL NOTICESHALF MOON BAY REVIEW sends a variety of e-mails to registered users who post listings. These e-mails include but are not limited to confirmations that a listing has been posted, notices that the listing is about to expire, and notices that the listing has been deleted by an administrator. These e-mails are a necessary feature for HALF MOON BAY REVIEW. If you do not want to receive such e-mail notices, please do not post a listing in HALF MOON BAY REVIEW.YOUR ROLE IN PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACYIf you share a computer terminal with others, you may want to consider establishing an anonymous e-mail account. In this way, e-mails that you receive from HALF MOON BAY REVIEW, such as password reminders, will be seen only by you. If you access HALF MOON BAY REVIEW through an e-mail account maintained by your employer, please note that it is possible that your employer may monitor your e-mail communications.NOTIFICATION OF CHANGESThis Privacy Statement may be revised over time as new features are added to HALF MOON BAY REVIEW or as Internet security and privacy standards evolve. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Statement each time you use HALF MOON BAY REVIEW, in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.CORRECTING & UPDATING INFORMATIONHALF MOON BAY REVIEW also permits you to correct or update personally identifiable information that you have previously provided to us. To do so, submit the changes directly through the site feature in question or send e-mail to: publisher@coastsidenewsgroup.com indicating the information that you wish to be corrected or updated.YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMSBy using this site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of HALF MOON BAY REVIEW Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the HALF MOON BAY REVIEW site and exit the site immediately. Your continued use of the WWW.HMBREVIEW.COM site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.CONTACTING USIf you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of the HALF MOON BAY REVIEW site, or your dealings with HALF MOON BAY REVIEW, you can contact us at any time by sending electronic mail to publisher@coastsidenewsgroup.com, or by sending a letter delivered by first class postage prepaid U.S. mail or overnight courier to the following address:Mailing Address:HALF MOON BAY REVIEW | 714 Kelly Avenue Half Moon Bay, CA 94019 | P: 650-726-4424
